

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

<u>■ gundydev@gmail.com</u>

• Grand Rapids, MI, United States

L 810-289-8430

Profile

Software Engineer. Typescript, NodeJS developer working within the web development industry for 3+ years. I am comfortable picking up anything related to NodeJS, React, and Typescript. Have intermediate Experience with C#. Confident in picking up any tool or language. Have an interest in Golang

Employment History

Software Engineer III, Generac - Tank Utility, Boston

September 2022 — Present

- Primarily migrated old angularJS 1 app to new CRA react app.
- Manage and implemented new features in angularJS 1.
- Refactored and improved many queries on express API and Firebase triggers.
- Led project discussions on how to best manage apps and keep them up to date.
- Introduced typescript and linting to new react applications.
- Integrated ReduxJS to handle vast global state slices and API features.
- Communicated with customers to best introduce wanted features and improvements to the application.
- Upgraded node versions and improved web pack configurations for old angularJS app to introduce many useful es features.
- Helped with Kubernetes cloud setup in AWS and better hosting of our services.
- Created various pipelines for all related applications for CI/CD and proper test support.
- Used Jest and RTL to test features and ensure proper scaling in the future.
- Duplicated our clustered environments to isolate and properly test.

Software Engineer II, RSI Logistics, Lansing, Michigan

September 2021 — September 2022

- Worked on and integrated C# GraphQL API into a React.JS application.
- Quality assurance with unit and e2e testing with Jest, React Testing Libarary, and Cypress.
- Migrated entire codebase to typescript.
- Created various forms and grids to display and validate data against user changes.
- Refactored how the company handles various states within the application and reduced bloat and tech debt throughout.
- Introduced proper documentation practices to excel collaboration within the team.

- Refactored various queries and procedures that face our MS SQL db to ensure better performance.
- Improved our CI/CD pipelines connected to github actions for faster builds and check results.
- Worked with thousands of rail related graphtypes and data models for client consumption.
- Iterated upon Wireframes, Mocks, and design documents with team members and SME's

Software Engineer, ProtoJet, Fraser, Michigan

March 2020 — June 2020

- Created SPA for rapid prototype manufacturing quote application.
- Worked with subject matter experts to define business rules and data models for the application.
- Worked with complicated engineering equations and algorithms to calculate quoting costs.
- Used prisma/apollo-server for the backend api and db hosted on a PM2 instance within AWS EC2 services.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Media and Information, Michigan State University, Lansing

September 2017 — September 2021

Heavy focus on user experience, data management, observation, and application. General IT information and application. Business communication.

Links

Personal Website (https://connorgunderson.vercel.app/)

Skills

Fast Learner Ability to Work in a Team

Typescript Node.js

React HTML & CSS (and preprocessors)

SQL noSQL

Clustering and Containerization (Docker & GraphQL

⁽⁸⁾ Full Stack Web Architecture (Monolithic &

Cloud Solutions (AWS & Azure) Microservice Hexagonal)

Version control with Git General IT and Linux

Cloud Computing (AWS & Azure) CI/CD with Github Actions

Testing Quality Assurance
Organization Skills Leadership Skills

Communication Skills Effective Time Management

References

Erik Gillespie from MSUEric Arbour from RSI Logisticserik.gillespie@gmail.comEArbour@rsilogistics.com